well I woke up couple weeks ago I had a
bruise on my side didn't run into
anything didn't get hit by anything just
got a bruise from supporting my own
weight at night apparently sleeping is
too much for me at this point this might
be my last show is what I'm telling you
folks so but I based my whole life on
ice cream as any normal person would
yeah yeah you don't have to be shy
there's a couple people pretending like
this crap behind me but no ice cream is
the real deal I base everything in my
life my favorite kind of ice cream is
called Neapolitan which if you don't
know Neapolitan is an Italian word that
means two good flavors one disgusting
one you hear that sound that's a room
divided by strawberries what that is
but you know the correct answer
strawberries the correct answer go with
your guts I don't know anything about
religion politics I hope you're not
looking for any guidance I don't have
any the only two things I know number
one strawberry ice cream sucks
and number two math is make-believe now
I know that second one makes me sound
stupid but is there any math teachers
here so I thought they're all wizards
it's yeah it's sorcery as far as I'm
concerned go back to Hogwarts with that
crap oh this isn't for dumb people I'm
not an idiot there's a certain amount of
math there's addition subtraction but
you remember you get around like seventh
eighth grade hey it started making stuff
up you know I'll tell you how you knew
when you got into class you went in
there as just all they stopped using
numbers in math anybody remember it's
going there it's all letters they were
like a plus B equals C Paul I think it's
done I don't know did I miss English
class is this a Scrabble challenge I
think I got a go even the unit sound
like they made it up that day you know
like this next units called guesstimates
he he
well you gotta do this guess the answers
Paul yeah it sounds easy but I got the
quiz back and I failed
I was like how I fail this is a guess oh
you didn't guess close enough I guess
mm-hmm and they said this was the kicker
the next unit was called the law of
diminishing returns this is how they
actually explained they said Paul you
know how you have one piece of cake the
second piece is good I said no I have no
idea what you're talking about you're
eating the wrong cake that's ridiculous